Guide to the Kenneth J. Arrow Papers, 1939-2011
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Committees and Consulting Series, 1980s-1990s.
  - Economic and Social Research Council (ESRC) (Box 9)
  - Economic Transition Group, (2 folders) (Box 40)
  - Einstein Archives (Box 9)
  - Elgar Best Papers (Box 40)
  - Electric Power Research Institute (EPRI) (Box 9)
  - Encyclopedia of Economics (Box 9)
  - Endowment for Excellence in Education (Box 40)
  - Energy: Next Twenty Years Study Group Members (Box 40)
  - The Esmee Fairbairn Research Center (Box 9)
  - European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) (Box 9)
  - European Bank for Reconstruction and Development, 1994-1998 (Box 40)
  - EBRD Paper (Box 40)
  - European University Institute (Box 9)
  - Fair Share (Box 9)
  - The Electric Rate Structure in Massachusetts (Box 9)
  - Federation of American Scientists (Box 9)
  - Federation of American Scientists, 1998-2001 (Box 40)
  - Fels Center of Government (Box 9)
  - Food Safety Council, Social and Economic Committee: Principles and Processes for Making Food Safety Decisions (Box 9)
  - Foundations and Applications of Utility, Risk, and Decision Theory (FUR) (Box 9)
  - France-Stanford Center (Box 40)
  - Gandhi Institute (Box 40)
  - Guggenheim (Box 40)
  - Haldi Associates (Box 9)
  - Hebrew University, (2 folders) (Box 40)
  - Hebrew University at Mount Scopus (Box 40)
  - Hewlett Packard (Box 40)
  - Hewlett Sustainability Project (Box 40)
  - Hoover Institution (Box 40)
  - INDECON (Box 40)
  - IDDRI (Box 40)
  - Institute for Economic Theory (Box 9)
  - Institut d'Etudes Politques de Paris (Box 9)
  - Institute of Medicine
    - Institute of Medicine, (2 folders) (Box 9)
    - Institute of Medicine, Committee on Environment (Box 10)
    - RBM Meeting, 2004 (Box 41)
    - Global Fund, WHO (Box 41)
    - Press (Box 41)
    - Under 5 Mortality Rates (Box 41)
    - Barat Study Report (Box 41)
    - General Background (Box 41)
    - Financing (Box 41)
    - Pre-report Correspondence (Antimalarial) (Box 41)
    - Antimalarial Study (Box 41)
    - Study Post-Report (Vaccines) (Box 41)
  - International Center for Economic Growth (Box 41)
  - International Center for Theoretical Physics (Box 41)
  - International Economics Association (IEA) (Box 10)
  - IEA-AEA
    - Booklet (The IEA: Past and Future) (Box 10)
    - Correspondence (Luc Fauvel, Jean Paul Fitoussi, Patricia Hillebrandt, Michael Kaser, Amartya Sen, Paulo Sylos Labini, Victor Urquidi) (Box 10)
  - IEA (Box 11)
    - Financial Advisory Committee - UNESCO (Box 11)
    - IEA Presidency (Box 41)
  - International Health Economics Society (Box 41)
  - International Institute for Applied Systems Analysis (Box 11)
  - International Society for Inventory Research (Box 11)
  - IPCC, 1995 (Box 41)
  - IPCC Review, 1999-2000 (Box 41)
  - Irvine Advisory (Box 11)
  - Israel English Language College (Box 11)
  - Jerusalem, Institute for Ethics and Economics (Box 11)
  - Jerusalem School of Economic Theory- New Director, 2008 (Box 41)
  - Jerusalem School of Economic Theory (Box 41)
  - Jet Propulsion Laboratory (Box 11)
  - Jewish Community Federation, 1982 (Box 41)
  - Jewish Community Federation-South Peninsula Campaign Cabinet, 1984 (Box 41)
  - Effectiveness of the Army (Box 11)
  - Kendall - World Bank (Box 41)
  - King's College (Box 11)
  - Maastricht Economic Research Institute on Innovation and Technology (MERIT) (Box 11)
  - MacArthur Foundation (Box 11)
  - MacArthur Foundation General (Box 41)
  - MacArthur Foundation Interaction Inequality (Box 41)
  - MacArthur Foundation - Economics (Box 41)
  - MacArthur Foundation Economic Initiative (Box 41)
  - MacArthur Foundation Social Interactions (Box 41)
  - Mattei Foundation (Fondazione Enrico Mattei) (Box 41)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS), (3 folders) (Box 11)
  - NAS (Box 12)
    - Advisory Committee (Box 41)
    - Budget and Internal Affairs - Government-University-Industry Roundtable (Box 12)
    - CHR, 2000-04 (Box 41)
    - Comments, 1998 (Box 41)
    - Commission on Human Rights (Box 41)
    - Environment TNG (Box 41)
    - Human Rights Committee (Box 12)
    - Markets and Organizations (Box 12)
    - Minorities (Box 12)
    - Nuclear War Committee (Estes Award) (Box 12)
    - Population Statement (Box 12)
    - PNAS (Box 41)
    - Review Prize (Box 41)
    - Section 43 (Box 41)
    - Status of Mathematics (Box 12)
    - Young-Foster, 2002 (Box 41)
  - National Medal of Science (Box 42)
  - National Research Council
    - Climatic Impact, (5 folders) (Box 12)
      - Cost-Benefit Analysis (Box 12)
      - Regulation (Box 12)
    - Office of Scientific and Engineering Personel (OSEP), 2000 (Box 42)
    - Policy and Global Affairs (PGA), 2002 (Box 42)
    - Report Review Committee, (2 folders) (Box 42)
  - National Committee for Full Employment (Box 12)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF) (Box 12)
  - NSF Anniversary Committee, 1999 (Box 42)
  - National Acid Precipitation Assessment Program (NAPAP) (Box 12)
  - National Acid Precipitation Assessment Program (NAPAP), (3 folders) (Box 13)
  - National Acid Precipitation Assessment Program (NAPAP), 1991 (Box 41)
  - National Oceanic and Atmospheric Association (NOAA) (Box 13)
  - National Oceanic and Atmospheric Association (NOAA)- Contingent Valuation, 1993 (Box 42)
  - Notes and Drafts (Box 13)
  - Nemetria (Box 42)
  - New Palgrave (Box 13)
  - New Palgrave-Money and Finance (Box 13)
  - Northeast Asia Forum (Box 13)
  - Omicron Delta Epsilon (Box 13)
  - Pew Center (Box 42)
  - Paris Ph.D. (Box 13)
  - Pontifical Academy, 1996-2009, (6 folders) (Box 42)
  - Poverty Institute (Box 13)
  - Pontifical Council for Justice and Peace (Box 13)
  - Price Institute (Box 13)
  - RAND-Contracts (Box 42)
  - RAND-Discount Rate (Box 13)
  - RAND-Graduate School (Box 13)
  - RAND-Graduate School, 1997 (Box 42)
  - Resources for the Future (RfF)-Role of Analysis in the Policy Process (Box 13)
  - RFF-AEI Benefit Cost (Box 42)
  - Riverside Case (Box 13)
  - Rothschild Prize (Box 42)
  - Samuelson 21st Century (Box 42)
  - Sant' Anna (Box 42)
  - Santa Fe Institute (Box 13)
  - Economics Program, General (Box 13)
  - Santa Fe Institute, (20 folders) (Box 14)
  - Santa Fe Institute-Summer Program (Box 14)
  - Seidman Award Selection Committee (Box 14)
  - Siedman Award, 1994-2000 (Box 42)
  - Sino-American Market Information Research Center at Stanford (SAMICS) (Box 14)
  - Sloan Foundation (Box 42)
  - Sloan Behavioral Economics Program (Box 14)
  - Society for the Advancement of Social-Economics (SASE) (Box 14)
  - Society for Benefit-Cost Analysis (Box 42)
  - Society for Social Choice and Welfare, 1997 (Box 42)
  - Social Science, Humanities, and Global Change (Box 42)
  - Stanford Center on Conflict and Negotiation (Box 14)
  - Stanford Center on Conflict and Negotiation (SCCN), 1992-1999 (Box 42)
  - SCCN Assessment (Box 42)
  - SCCN Book, 1999 (Box 42)
  - Stanford Institute of Theoretical Economics (SITE) (Box 14)
  - SITE, 1997 (Box 42)
  - SITE, 2000 (Box 42)
  - Stanford Research Institute (Box 42)
  - Suppes Forecasts (Box 42)
  - SUNY Stonybrook (Box 42)
  - Talmudic Economics (Box 42)
  - Tinbergen Institute/ International Journal of Development Planning Literature (Box 14)
  - Tobin Project (Box 42)
  - Underground Classics (Box 42)
  - Urban Institute (Box 42)
  - US Council of Economic Advisors- Civilian Technology, 1961-62 (Box 42)
  - USSR Institute of Control Sciences (Box 14)
  - Visitation Committee for Graduate Program, Review of Department of Economics at the University of Massachusetts, Amherst (Box 14)
  - Western Economic Association Nominating Committee (Box 14)
  - Wharton Risk and Decision Processes Center Advisory Committee (Box 14)
  - Wharton Risk and Decision Processes Center Advisory Committee (Box 15)
  - Wharton Risk, 1986-1988 (Box 42)
  - World Bank (Box 15)
  - World Institute for Development Economics Research (WIDER) (Box 15)
  - World Resources Institute (Box 15)
  - Yale Program on Non-Profit Organizations (Box 15)
  - Journals Subseries
    - American Economic Review (Box 15)
    - American Economic Review - Top 20 (Box 42)
    - American Prospect (Box 15)
    - Bell Journal (Box 15)
    - Business in the Contemporary World (Box 15)
    - Complexity (Box 15)
    - Economics and Philosophy (Box 15)
    - Fundamentals of Economics (Box 15)
    - Group Decision and Negotiation Journal (Box 15)
    - Journal of Complexity (Box 15)
    - Journal of Corporate and Industrial History (Box 15)
    - Journal of Health Economics (Box 15)
    - Journal of Mathematical Economics (Box 15)
    - Journal of Mathematical Economics, 1994-2002 (Box 42)
    - Journal of Official Statistics (Box 15)
    - Industrial and Corporate Change (Box 15)
    - Information Economics and Policy (Box 15)
    - Lux Mundi (Box 15)
    - Mathematics in Education (Box 15)
    - Mathematics of Operations Research (Box 15)
    - Organization Science (Box 15)
    - Philosophy and Public Affairs (Box 15)
    - Review of Economics and Statistics (Box 15)
    - Science (Box 15)
    - Social Choice and Welfare (Box 42)
    - Society for Research in Economics (Box 15)
    - Stochastic Analysis and Applications (Box 15)
    - THESIS (Box 42)
  - Expert Witness Subseries
    Professor Arrow acted as an expert witness in several court cases in the State of Calornia and nationally. Several of these cases are restricted.
    - Asbestos Insurance Coverage Cases, 1985, (5 booklets) (Box 43)
    - AT&T Case, 1982 (Box 43)
    - Bell Atlantic-GTE Merger, 1998, (2 folders) (Box 43)
    - Burlington, 2000 (Box 43)
    - Commonwealth Edison, 1987 (Box 43)
    - Copper Case, 2001 (Box 43)
    - Dupont Report, 1980 (Box 43)
    - Evergreen vs NCR Comten, 1985 (Box 43)
    - FNMA, 1992 (Box 43)
    - LAX Airport Fee, 1995 (Box 43)
    - Litton vs Honeywell, 1997 (Box 43)
    - McDermott, 1986 (Box 43)
    - Microsoft Antitrust, 1994 (Box 43)
    - Orange County vs Merrill Lynch, 1998 (Box 43)
    - Pharmaceutical Anti-trust, 1995 (Box 43)
    - Phillips Petroleum Company, 1985 (Box 43)
    - Polypropylene Anti-trust, 1999 (Box 43)
    - RBOC Manufacturing, 1991 (Box 43)
    - San Francisco Foundation, 1985 (Box 43)
    - Shell Oil Company, 1987 (Box 43)
    - Steel Imports, 1993 (Box 43)
    - SPCC vs AT&T, 1982 (Box 43)
    - Telecommunications Regulation, 1984 (Box 43)
    - Trans-Alaskan Pipeline, 1978-1983, (3 folders) (Box 43)
    - US vs Microsoft, 2002 (Box 43)
    - US vs Western Electric and AT&T, 1991 (Box 43)
    - USAir Inc. et al. vs American Airlines, Inc. and United Airlines, Inc., 1988, (2 folders) (Box 43)
    - Verizon, 2003 (Box 44)
    - Williams Pipeline, 1979, (2 folders) (Box 44)
    - Restricted Expert Witness Materials (Box 45-47)
      Access Restricted.
      - Chichilnisky vs Wooders, 1994, (17 folders) (Box 45, 46)
      - IBM vs Seagate, 1995 (Box 47)
      - Railroad Cases, 1986 (Box 47)
      - Sun vs Microsoft, 1998 (Box 47)
      - Warner-Polygram FTC, 1984 (Box 47)
- Politics and Activism Series, 1974-1994.
  Contains files of Professor Arrow's personal political activities. These include especially work for peace in the Middle East, for arms control, in support of human rights and dissidents, and with other causes. These are collected in the Middle East, Arms Control, Human Rights and Miscellaneous Involvements Subseries, respectively. It also includes a UNESCO Subseries for his work for that organization.
  - Middle East Subseries (Box 15)
    - American Professors for Peace in the Middle East (APPME) ( Oil and the Arab-Israeli Power Balance by Arrow), 1977-90 (Box 15)
    - Beyond War, 1987-91 (Box 15)
    - International Center for Peace in the Middle East, 1988-91 (Box 15)
    - International Center for Peace in the Middle East, 1996 (Box 48)
    - Israel Democracy Institute (IDI), 1990-92 (Box 15)
    - Israel-Diaspora Institute (IDI), 1990 (Box 15)
    - Iraq Statement, 2003 (Box 48)
    - Mid-East Center for Economic and Institutional Development, 1989-90 (Box 15)
    - Middle East Policy (Includes correspondence with George McGovern), 1992 (Box 15)
    - Middle East, 1973-1988 (Box 48)
  - Arms Control Subseries (Box 15)
    - Center for International Security and Arms Control, 1985-90 (Box 15)
    - Coalition for a Comprehensive Test Ban, 1993 (Box 15)
    - Economics of Arms and Disarmament, 1989-91 (Box 15)
    - Economics of Arms Reduction, 1991-93 (Box 15)
    - Economists Against the Arms Race, (7 folders) (Box 16)
      - General, 1987-1993 (Box 15)
      - General, 1993-2002 (Box 48)
      - Haiffa Conference, 1994 (Box 16)
      - Notre Dame Conference ( The Basic Economics of Arms Reduction and A Note on the Peace Dividend and Reallocation of Knowledge Skills by Arrow), 1990-91 (Box 16)
    - Economists Allied for Arms Reduction (Box 48)
      - Kashmir, 1994 (Box 48)
      - Nuclear Statement, 2002 (Box 48)
      - Russia, 1998 (Box 48)
    - Gardels Statement, 1999 (Box 48)
    - National Research Council (NRC)-Nuclear War Committee, 1987-93 (Box 16)
    - Union of Concerned Scientists, 1982-85 (Box 16)
  - Human Rights Subseries
    - Aurora Foundation, 1987 (Box 16)
    - Baha'i in Iran, 1982-83 (Box 16)
    - Chili, 1976-79 (Box 16)
    - Committee for Concerned Scientists, 1981-87 (Box 16)
    - Committee for International Academic Freedom, 1992 (Box 16)
    - Dissidents, 1974-91 (Box 16)
    - Dissidents- Ida Nudel, 1978-79 (Box 16)
    - El Salvador and Central America, 1984-90 (Box 16)
    - South Africa, 1988 (Box 16)
  - UNESCO Subseries, 1970s, (3 folders) (Box 16)
  - UNESCO Subseries, (9 folders) (Box 17)
  - UNESCO Council on the Future, 1999-2003 (Box 48)
  - Miscellaneous Involvements Subseries (Box 17)
    - American Council for an Energy-Efficient Economy, 1982-87 (Box 17)
    - Balanced Budget Amendment, 1982-97 (Box 48)
    - Brown for Governor, 1994 (Box 48)
    - Childright Initiative, 1994 (Box 48)
    - Clean Air Statement by Nobel Laureates, 1989 (Box 17)
    - Clinch River Nuclear Breeder Reactor, 1983 (Box 17)
    - Clinton Campaign, 1992 (Box 17)
    - Croatia, 1991 (Box 48)
    - Current Wisdom, 1988 (Box 17)
    - Cutler Amicus Curiae, 2010 (Box 48)
    - Dartmouth Prospect, 1993 (Box 17)
    - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee, 1975-78 (Box 17)
    - Democratic Study Group, 1983 (Box 17)
    - Drash, 1987 (Box 17)
    - Earth Day, 1990 (Box 17)
    - Economic Conversion Center, 1993 (Box 17)
    - Economic Security Seminar, 1991 (Box 17)
    - Economists for Peace and Security (Box 48)
    - European Network, 2001 (Box 48)
    - Food and Disarmament International, 1981-87 (Box 17)
    - Gore, Sen. Albert (Economics Lecture), 1990-91 (Box 17)
    - Heritage of Mankind, 1980-91 (Box 17)
    - Hillel, 1980-92 (Box 17)
    - Institute for Civil Justice, 1980-87 (Box 17)
    - Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change (IPCC), 1994 (Box 48)
    - Minimum Wage Initiative, 1996 (Box 48)
    - NAACP Legal Defense Fund- DuPont Case, 1993 (Box 17)
    - National Committee on American Foreign Policy, Inc., 1981 (Box 17)
    - National Institute of Economics and Law, 1982-83 (Box 17)
    - Norweigian Climate Change, 2009-2010 (Box 48)
    - Nova Specs, 1987-89 (Box 17)
    - Nuclear Reactor Correspondence, 1974 (Box 17)
    - Oregon Discrimination Case, 1983 (Box 17)
    - PCL Initiative, 1998 (Box 48)
    - Planned Parenthood, 1982 (Box 17)
    - Proposition 35-Balanced Budget Amendment, 1984 (Box 17)
    - Public Interest Economics, 1981-85 (Box 17)
    - Public Statements, 1985-94 (Box 17)
    - Public Statements, 1994-2011, (5 folders) (Box 48)
    - Real Peace, 1988 (Box 17)
    - Redefining Progress, 1997 (Box 48)
    - Sunstein Nomination, 2009 (Box 48)
- Correspondence and Personal Files Series, 1980s-1990s.
  Contains files on various individuals. While the series is characterized mostly by correspondence, some files are primarily correspondence with the person, while others are primarily correspondence about the person, such as letters of recommendation or tenure reviews. Additions to the collection are housed in boxes 48-49, but files have been incorporated intellectually in the folder list below.
  RESTRICTED
  - A, misc. (Box 18)
  - Abramovitz, Moses (Box 18)
  - Abramovitz, Moses, Introductory remarks to his presidential address (Box 18)
  - Adam, Christopher (Box 18)
  - Adelman, Irma, 1973 (Box 18)
  - Adelstein, Richard (Box 18)
  - Admati, Anat (Box 18)
  - Ahmad, Maqsood (Box 18)
  - Alexander, Charles (Box 18)
  - Allais, Professor Maurice (Box 18)
  - Allen, Beth (Box 18)
  - Allen, William R. (Box 18)
  - Amemiya, Takeshi (Box 18)
  - Amsel, Professor George (Box 18)
  - Anderson, Richard M. (Box 18)
  - Aoki, Masahiko (Box 18)
  - Araujo, Aloisio, 1977-79 (Box 18)
  - Archibald, Christopher (Box 18)
  - Arney, Richard (Box 18)
  - Arthur, Brian, 1993 (Box 18)
  - Attali, Jacques (Box 18)
  - Augier, Mie (Box 48)
  - Aumann, Rips (Box 18)
  - Aumann, Robert (Box 18)
  - Ausubel, Lawrence Marc (Box 18)
  - B, misc. (Box 18)
  - Ba-Be, misc (Box 48)
  - Bacharach, Michael (Box 18)
  - Bacharach, Michael, Visiting Jan-March, 1976 (Box 18)
  - Baker, John Charles (Box 18)
  - Balinski, Michel (Box 18)
  - Bangert, Harold W. (Box 18)
  - Barclay, Michael J. (Box 18)
  - Batement, Bradley W. (Box 18)
  - Bauer, Peter Lord (Box 18)
  - Bell, Daniel (Box 18)
  - Beltramo, Daniel (Box 18)
  - Berman, José (Box 18)
  - Bernheim, Douglas (Box 18)
  - Bewley, Truman (Box 18)
  - Bh-By, misc (Box 48)
  - Biggar, Darryl R. (Box 18)
  - Birardi, Franco, 2 folders (Box 18)
  - Bjerval, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Blanco, Dr. Cicely Woods (Box 18)
  - Boldrin, Michele (Box 18)
  - Boorman, Scott A., 5 folders (Box 18)
  - Boxer, Nancy (Box 19)
  - Brandenburger, Adam (Box 19)
  - Bradford, David (Box 19)
  - Bradford, Richard M. (Box 19)
  - Brannon, Kevin (Box 48)
  - Breit, William (Box 19)
  - Brenner, Reuven (Box 19)
  - Bresnahan Review (Box 19)
  - Brock, Horace W. (Box 19)
  - Brock, William A. (Box 19)
  - Brode, John (Box 19)
  - Broome, John (Box 19)
  - Brown, Donald (Box 19)
  - Browne, Elizabeth A. (Box 48)
  - Bubna, Amit (Box 48)
  - C, misc. (Box 19)
  - C, misc. (Box 48)
  - Campbell, Donald, 2 folders (Box 19)
  - Cardell, Nicholas Scott (Box 19)
  - Carlton, Dennis WM. (Box 19)
  - Chang, Dr. Chih (Box 19)
  - Chang, David (Box 19)
  - Chang, Sheldon (Box 19)
  - Caspar, President Gerhard (Box 19)
  - Cheung, Rayner (Box 19)
  - Chichilnisky, Garciela (Box 19)
  - Chikan, Attila (Box 19)
  - Chinn, Dr. Dennis (Box 19)
  - Chipman, John S. (Box 19)
  - Chomsky, Noam (Box 19)
  - Clarke, Richard, 2 folders (Box 19)
  - Clay, Karen (Box 19)
  - Cogan Appointment (Box 19)
  - Cooper, Leon N. (Box 19)
  - Cooter, Robert D. (Box 19)
  - Costrell, Robert, Income Determination: or, what Keynes means to me, 2 folders (Box 19)
  - Costrell, Robert (Box 19)
  - Crampton, Graham R. (Box 19)
  - Coughlin, Peter (Box 19)
  - Courtillot, E.P. (Box 19)
  - Courtillot, Professor Vincent (Box 19)
  - D, misc. (Box 19)
  - D, misc. (Box 48)
  - D'Amico, Thomas F. (Box 19)
  - Dasgupta Appointment (Box 20)
  - Davis, Donald B. (Box 20)
  - David, Paul (Box 20)
  - Day, Richard (Box 20)
  - Day, Colin (Box 20)
  - Debreu, Gerard, 2 folders (Box 20)
  - Despres (Box 20)
  - De Croix, Gregroy A. (Box 20)
  - DeMarzo, Peter M. (Box 20)
  - Dieffenbach, Bruce (Box 20)
  - Dieffenbach References (Box 20)
  - Diewert, W. Erwin (Box 20)
  - Dionne, Georges (Box 20)
  - Dohner, Robert S. (Box 20)
  - Douglas, Aaron, 4 folders (Box 20)
  - Douglas, Aaron, Biographical Sketch (Box 20)
  - Dowe, Douglas, 1984 (Box 20)
  - Dreze, Jean (Box 20)
  - Dudkin, Professor Lev (Box 20)
  - Duffie, Darrell (Box 20)
  - Durlauf, Steven (Box 20)
  - E, misc. (Box 20)
  - Engelbrecht, Richard (Box 20)
  - Ellsberg, Daniel (Box 20)
  - Etheredge, Lloyd S. (Box 20)
  - Erickson, James (Box 20)
  - Ersel, Hasan (Box 20)
  - Eliasson, Gunnar (Box 20)
  - F, misc. (Box 20)
  - Fang, Weiwu (Box 20)
  - Feiger, George (Box 20)
  - Fels, Rendigs (Box 20)
  - Feiwel, George R., 2 folders (Box 20)
  - Fischbeck, Paul (Box 20)
  - Friedman, Milton, 2 folders (Box 20)
  - Fuchs, Victor R. (Box 20)
  - Futia, Carl (Box 20)
  - G, misc. (Box 20)
  - G, misc. (Box 49)
  - Geanokoplos, John, 2 folders (Box 20)
  - Geanakoplos, John (Box 49)
  - Geevarghese, Anna Susan (Box 20)
  - Gevers, Louis (Box 20)
  - Ghosh, Sen (Box 49)
  - Giarini (Box 20)
  - Gibbard, Alan (Box 20)
  - Gibbons, Robert (Box 20)
  - Ginsburg, Bill (Box 21)
  - Ginzberg, Eli (Box 21)
  - Glustoff, Earl (Box 21)
  - Goldman, Beila S., 5 folders (Box 21)
  - Gordon, Nancy (Box 21)
  - Gordon, Tracy (Box 21)
  - Gorman, William M. (Box 21)
  - Gould, F.J. (Box 21)
  - Gould, Mark (Box 21)
  - Gould, Stephen J. (Box 21)
  - Grandmont, Jean-Michel (Box 21)
  - Green, Jerry, 2 folders (Box 21)
  - Greenberg, Joseph (Box 21)
  - Grossman, Sanford (Box 21)
  - Gul, Faruk (Box 21)
  - Gurfel (Box 21)
  - H, misc. (Box 21)
  - H, misc. (Box 49)
  - Hadfield, Gillian K. (Box 21)
  - Hahn, Frank, 2 folders (Box 21)
  - Hahn, Frank (Box 49)
  - Hammond, Peter J. (Box 21)
  - Han, Aaron K. (Box 21)
  - Harcourt, Dr. Geoffrey (Box 21)
  - Harris, Donald (Box 21)
  - Harris, Jeffrey (Box 21)
  - Harris, Milton (Box 21)
  - Harsanyi, John C. (Box 21)
  - Harsanyi, John (Box 49)
  - Hart, Oliver (Box 21)
  - Hassin, Rafael (Box 21)
  - Hayabusa, Nagahara (Box 21)
  - Hayashi, Toshihiko (Box 21)
  - Heal, Geoffrey (Box 21)
  - Heller, Walter P. (Box 21)
  - Heiner, Ron (Box 21)
  - Helpman, Elhanan (Box 21)
  - Hess, Jim (Box 21)
  - Hicks, Michael, 2 folders (Box 21)
  - Hillas, John (Box 21)
  - Hiromatsu, Takeshi (Box 21)
  - Hirshleifer, Professor Jack (Box 21)
  - Hirshman, Albert O. (Box 21)
  - Holland, John (Box 21)
  - Hollis, Martin (Box 21)
  - Holstrom, Bengt (Box 21)
  - Honkapohja, Seppo (Box 21)
  - Hotelling Obituary (Box 22)
  - Huang, Peter H., 2 folders (Box 22)
  - Huang, Peter H. (Box 49)
  - Hudson, Ed (Box 22)
  - Hu, Wei-Yin (Box 22)
  - Hurwicz, Leonid (Box 22)
  - Hylland, Aanund (Box 22)
  - I, misc. (Box 22)
  - Intrilligator, Michael (Box 22)
  - Ishikawa, Tsuneo, 2 folders (Box 22)
  - J, misc. (Box 22)
  - J, misc. (Box 49)
  - Jamison, Dean (Box 22)
  - Jimbo, Ichiro (Box 22)
  - Jonscher, Charles, 2 folders (Box 22)
  - Jubeir, Maher (Box 22)
  - K, misc. (Box 22)
  - K, misc. (Box 49)
  - Kalfon, Pierre (Box 22)
  - Kalman, Peter (Box 22)
  - Kalt, Joseph (Box 22)
  - Kamoike, Osamu (Box 49)
  - Kandori, Michihiro (Box 22)
  - Kaneko, Mamoru (Box 22)
  - Kantorovich, Acad. L.V. (Box 22)
  - Karlin, Samuel (Box 22)
  - Karni, Edi (Box 22)
  - Kast, Robert (Box 22)
  - Kelly, Jerry S. (Box 22)
  - Kelsey, David (Box 22)
  - Kennedy, David (Box 22)
  - Kennedy, Joan and John (Box 22)
  - Kirman, Alan (Box 22)
  - Kitching, Professor Beverly (Box 22)
  - Kneese and Krutilla (Box 22)
  - Koenig, Evan (Box 22)
  - Kohlberg, Elon (Box 22)
  - Koopmans (Box 22)
  - Kornai Appointment (Box 22)
  - Kreps, David (Box 22)
  - Kreicher, Larry (Box 22)
  - Krenzin, Kenneth Thomas (Box 22)
  - Kumar, Praveen (Box 22)
  - Kunreuther, Howard (Box 22)
  - Kuran, Timur (Box 22)
  - Kurz, Mordecai (Box 22)
  - Kurz, Mordecai (Box 49)
  - Kurz Dinner (Box 22)
  - L, misc. (Box 22)
  - L, misc. (Box 49)
  - Laffront, Jean-Jacques (Box 22)
  - Lai, Edwin (Box 22)
  - Landau, Ralph (Box 22)
  - Landes, David (Box 22)
  - Lane, John (Box 22)
  - Lang, Serge (Box 49)
  - Laroque, Guy (Box 22)
  - Lay, Joseph (Box 22)
  - Lederberg (Box 22)
  - Ledyard, John (Box 22)
  - Lave, Charles (Box 22)
  - Leland, Hayne Ellis (Box 23)
  - Leonard, Robert J. (Box 23)
  - Lesourne, Jacques (Box 23)
  - Leverich, Brian E. (Box 23)
  - Levhari, David (Box 23)
  - Levin, Harvey J. (Box 23)
  - Levinthal, Daniel (Box 23)
  - Levitt, Paul R., 2 folders (Box 23)
  - Levy-Garboua, Vivien (Box 23)